♪ MTV ♪
[both chuckling]
[rock music]
♪ ♪
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
So we know that the
inverse angle is
the same as the...
[drill droning]
Beavis. what are you doing?
Uh. nothing. [drill drones]
You must have heard
something else.
[drill droning]
Beavis. put your drill away
before I confiscate it. mm-kay?
Yeah. Beavis.
Some of these dumbasses
are trying to learn.
[chuckles]
- Okay. yeah.
It won't happen again.
[sighs] Okay. So
the inverse...
[drill droning]
Sorry. sorry. [chuckles]
I'm... I'm just
gonna put it away.
[drill drones]
See? I can't even reach
it. [drill drones]
Okay. go ahead. Yeah.
You were saying some
angles or something.
[snickers]
[sighs] So the inverse
angle is the same...
[drill drones]
Oh. sorry. sorry. I forgot.
[chuckles] It
won't happen again.
He means it this time.
sir. [drill droning]
I'm putting this
in my desk. Beavis.
You can have it back at the
end of the week. mm-kay?
[school bell rings]
Um. Butt-Head.
how're we gonna get
the drill back?
[chuckles]
- Uh... whoa.
I got an idea. Beavis.
We can go. like.
hide in that box
until school's closed.
and then we can
go get the drill.
Yeah. yeah. Good idea. Yeah.
[chuckles]
[chuckles] [both snicker]
This is gonna be cool.
- Scoot over. [chuckles]
- We're beating the system.
When we get the drill back.
I'm gonna. like.
drill holes in stuff.
[both chuckle]
- Good idea. Beavis.
[chuckles] Drill.
- [chuckles]
[both snickering]
What's going on. Butt-Head?
Uh. I don't know. [chuckles]
[both grunting]
Aah. aah. oh. aah. Ow. ow.
Aah. aah. aah. my
eye. Ow. ow. aah. aah.
[grunts]
Glad that's over.
I think. like. a big truck
went by or something.
That was really
starting to piss me...
Ow. aah. aah.
[clank]
Okay. Beavis.
it sounds like
everybody's gone now.
Let's go check and see
if the coast is clear.
[grunting]
Um. Butt-Head.
I can't get out of
the box. [chuckles]
Uh. this sucks.
[chuckles]
[whispering] Hello. everybody.
It's... Gibi.
Welcome back to my channel.
I'm gonna start with...
- What is this. Butt-Head?
A fairly simple item.
[whispering] It's called ASMR.
You know. this is. uh...
This is actually
kind of relaxing.
You need to speak
more quietly. Beavis.
Yeah. sorry.
[softly] This is kind
of relaxing. Butt-Head.
You know what I mean?
[chuckles] Yes. I do.
It's putting me to
sleep. [chuckles]
This is a baby pink...
I kind of like talking
like this. Butt-Head.
I think I'm gonna talk like
this for the rest of my life.
Oh. yeah. yeah.
I bet chicks like it. too.
[chuckles] Ooh.
I didn't even think
of that. [chuckles]
Hey. baby.
would you like to
come back to my place?
I can talk even
quieter than this.
You won't even know
I'm in the room.
[chuckles]
Oh. yeah. [chuckles]
Boing. [snickers]
Not fully. like. color
organized or anything.
[clears throat] Butt-Head...
listen. watching this video
is kind of giving
me wood. [chuckles]
Uh. I don't need to
hear about that. Beavis.
[chuckles quietly]
Butt-Head...
I think I might have
to spank my monkey.
[chuckles]
Beavis. I am going to kick
the living bejesus out of you
if you try to spank your monkey.
I have to.
Butt-Head. [chuckles]
It's the ASMR.
I can't do anything about it.
[chuckles]
- This kind of sound.
Beavis. I don't want to hear
about your boner. so shut up.
I'm trying to watch this ASMR.
Do not spank your monkey.
[soft clicking]
Butt-Head...
I think those magic markers
are giving me a boner.
Damn it. Beavis. I'm
gonna change the channel
if you don't stop talking
about your boners.
Ooh. um...
Butt-Head. that. um...
That smack kind of
made my scalp tingle.
Can you smack me again like
that. just really gently?
Uh. no. Beavis.
[normal voice] What'd
you say. Butt-Head? Aah!
[normal voice] Damn it.
Beavis. you ruined everything.
Oh. yeah. sorry.
- Uh. help?
- Help!
Help!
- Hey. you buttholes.
open the box.
I think. like.
no one can hear us or something.
Damn it. Beavis. you
got us stuck in here.
Yeah. sorry. [chuckles]
Hang on. I need to
scratch my butt.
[chuckles] Damn it. [grunts]
Ugh. ugh.
Ah. there we go.
Wait. was that your
butt or my butt?
[chuckles]
- Uh... I don't know.
I think it might have
been my hand. actually.
Beavis. you better get your hand
off whoever's butt it is.
Sorry. Butt-Head.
I can't hear you.
My butt's in your face.
It's. like. muffling the sound.
[sighs] That does it. asswipe.
[grunting]
- Ow. Cut it out. butthole.
[grunts]
Beavis. I'm gonna kick
your ass all over this box.
Cut it out! Ow. ow. [grunts]
[grunting] Ow.
- [grunts]
- Ow. ow.
[sighs] [chuckles]
You know. um. maybe we
should just. like. get used
to living in this box.
you know? [chuckles]
It's not that bad. really.
It's kind of growing on
me. actually. [chuckles]
Beavis. I'm gonna kill you.
Maybe life is better
in the box. you know?
Maybe we'll meet some
chicks in here or something.
There's no chicks
in the box. dumbass.
Well. not now. but.
you know. like...
Maybe if we were more
outgoing. you know?
My head's gonna kick your ass.
[grunts]
- Ow.
Ow. Eh. my butt! Aah! Stop!
Ow.
- [grunts]
- Ow!
[both groaning]
I don't want to be in this
box anymore. Butt-Head.
It sucks.
It's getting kind
of hard to breathe.
[chuckles] Hard.
No. no. really. Butt-Head.
I think we're. like. running
out of air or something.
We need to stop breathing
so we don't run out.
[gasping]
Hey. stop. What are you doing?
I'm gonna breathe
all of it. Beavis.
[panting]
Stop it. Butt-Head. come on.
Quit hogging the air.
Get your own air. dumbass.
No. I'm gonna strangle
you to save air.
Damn it.
Quit moving your neck
so I can strangle it.
Damn it. Beavis.
stop strangling me.
Not till you promise
to stop breathing air.
Never. [both grunting]
Whoa.
Butt-Head. look. we're free.
Whoa. Good job. Beavis.
Now all we gotta do
is... [both groan]
- Beavis?
- Yeah?
You're a dumbass.
[both chuckle]
- [grunts]
♪ ♪
Trees suck. [chuckles]
Yeah. I don't like
leaves either.
[chuckles] They suck.
[chuckles]
Yeah. look at that.
He's grabbing his
schlong in Spanish.
[chuckles]
[snickers]
Uh. these boy bands
always have. like.
one really smart one.
one ugly one. and.
uh. three other dudes.
[chuckling]
He's the smart one. [chuckles]
Are these guys. like.
lumberjacks or something?
[chuckles]
We've come to chop
down your trees.
And then we will make
love to your women.
[chuckles]
Yeah. first I take your
wood. and then I have wood.
[snickering]
[singing in Spanish]
Where are they
anyway? [chuckles]
That looks like the woods
back behind Pizza Hut.
Yeah. there are a lot
of mosquitos back there.
[chuckles] I was
back there once.
and a mosquito bit me
right on my schlong.
What were you doing
with your schlong out
behind Pizza Hut?
That part of the story's
not important. Butt-Head.
[chuckles]
- Uh... yeah it is.
You know. I was just. like.
spraying it with
OFF!. you know?
Didn't work. [chuckles]
- Uh...
- Anyway. that's not important.
What's important is
my schlong itched
for. like. two days.
And I tried to
scratch it in class.
and everyone thought I
was spanking my monkey.
[chuckles]
Uh... but you were
spanking your monkey.
No. I was scratching
a mosquito bite
on my schlong. [chuckles]
And then. you know. um.
while I was in the area.
you know. one thing
led to another.
You know. but. um...
But it was the mosquito's fault
that I was in that area
in the first place.
Stupid bug. [both snicker]
Uh. Beavis?
There's a mosquito on
your face right now.
- Really?
- Hang on. hang on. hold still.
I'll get it for you.
- [groans]
- [chuckles]
- So did you get it?
Uh. wait a second. He's back.
Damn it. Butt-Head.
you gotta hit harder.
Nope. It's still there.
[grunting]
He's a tough little
fella. [grunting]
- Is it gone now?
- Uh. no.
I know something
that'll kill him.
[chuckles]
Uh. let's see here.
Uh. there it is. [chuckles]
This ought to work.
Now hold absolutely
still. Beavis.
[chuckles] Don't move.
Are you gonna
spray that on my...
[grunting]
- [chuckles]
- Damn it. Butt-Head.
- Not how that works.
Okay. class. Beavis
and Butt-Head
have now been
missing for a week.
If anyone has any info.
please contact the
authorities. mm-kay?
On a lighter note.
we've covered an
incredible amount of math
in the last week.
and we can finally start
working at grade level.
which is why we've brought
in these new textbooks.
Don't worry. everyone
will get one.
Oh. my.
[both grunting]
[coughing]
[coughs]
Whoa.
- Where are we? [chuckles]
- Oh. hey.
Hey. it worked. It
worked. Butt-Head.
[chuckles]
I'll just go ahead
and get this from you.
[drill droning]
[chuckles] That was cool.
[chuckles]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm